Look at the cake. It's so pretty.
- I guess he's proposing to her.
- I guess so.
It's so pretty.
Hey.
Hey. You got the wrong table.
- No?
- No.
Over here.
I'm sorry.
- It's so pretty.
- I'm jealous.
- I guess it's them.
- What's this?
- Goodness.
- I'm sorry.
- It's so pretty.
- I'm jealous.
- That's pretty.
- What's this?
Soo-jin, will you marry me?
Say yes.
- Say yes.
For me, marriage was a natural thing
to do when the time came.
Like how flowers bloom in spring
and how the rainy season brings
a downpour of rain in summer,
it was in the course of nature.
With the rainy season approaching,
the sweltering heat is in full swing.
It will continue to be hot
until the weekend
when the rainy season begins.
However, as the climate is changing
and the uncertainty
of weather forecasting is increasing…
He's so cool.
Why is he taking such a risk?
What?
- I'm jealous.
- He's really cool.
Well, it's too noisy here.
Should we go now?
Okay.
Is there anything
that we can take for granted?
No way.
How is it possible?
They're dating?
You must be mistaken.
I saw them with my own eyes.
I saw Ha-kyung and Si-woo
eating and drinking together.
They're on the same team.
So isn't that normal?
And Ha-kyung isn't Si-woo's type.
He isn't her type either.
She'd never like anyone
so haughty and reckless.
Exactly.
The two of them dating is nonsense.
Jeez.
I'm sure
Si-woo approached Ha-kyung
to get back at me.
What are you saying?
Si-woo oppa is unpredictable,
but he'd never do that.
"Oppa"?
Did you just call him oppa?
I take it back. It was my mistake.
Anyway, he isn't that kind of person.
I see. If he isn't,
why did he do this to my face?
- That's because you--
- Hey.
Don't side with that jerk.
What?
Do you have something to say?
Anyway, they aren't together.
So don't drag other people
into our problem.
I'm telling you, it's true.
He's trying to get back at me!
By the way, earlier--
What do you want to do on the weekend?
- What?
- It's our weekend off.
Do you want to do anything?
Well, I don't know.
Do you want to see a movie?
The new horror movie
that's coming out looks good.
All right.
We can go for a drive too.
That sounds good too.
Or we can work out together.
You run, don't you?
That sounds good too.
Or we can just go grocery shopping.
Sure.
Why do you say yes to everything?
- What?
- You sound so unenthusiastic.
You said yes to all my suggestions.
I'm really okay with anything.
Actually, I'm happy just walking with you.
I am too,
but let's do something special
on the weekend.
What do you want to do?
Well…
there are so many things I want to do.
I want to go to
the glow-in-the-dark bowling alley.
I want to go on a trip to Jeju--
No, too many people go there
for their honeymoon,
so I'll pass.
What's wrong with that?
Doesn't it feel a little suffocating?
What's suffocating about it?
"The end of love is marriage."
Such an obvious conclusion
isn't the only answer.
But the honeymooners act like
they're the ones who got the right answer.
Not everyone is like that,
but it looks a bit suffocating.
Stay here. I'll get something to drink.
- Okay.
EPISODE 9
DRY CHANGMA (RAINY SEASON)
INNOVATIVE WEATHER SERVICES
A STEPPING STONE TO PUBLIC SAFETY
A stationary front has formed
on the southern coast of Jeju,
and it's expected to rain starting
from Jeju early tomorrow morning.
The moving speed
of the stationary front is 35km/h,
which aligns with our initial forecast.
- Did you say 35?
- Yes.
At this rate, it'll start to rain
in the metropolitan area tomorrow evening
as we first predicted, right?
Yes, sir.
- What about the press?
- Yes.
Because of the prolonged heatwave,
they're looking forward
to the rainy season.
Is that so?
Okay.
Proceed with the press briefing
as scheduled and let's move on.
Okay. Jeju Office?
All right.
Good work.
- Good work.
NATIONAL METEOROLOGICAL CENTER
COMPREHENSIVE CONTROL SYSTEM
May I have a word with you?
Are you dating Lee Si-woo?
What?
What did you say?
I saw you two together.
The restaurant that
I took you to for drinks.
You two were there.
Oh, that day.
Si-woo and I are on the same team.
Can't colleagues drink together?
Did that look like we were dating?
No.
You two kissing made it
look like you were dating.
You're crazy.
Ha-kyung, you've changed so much.
When you were with me,
you hated public displays of affection.
But you kissed him openly at a restaurant.
I knew there was something
when you two bickered.
I thought it was weird
when you pulled him aside,
so I followed you,
and you were very affectionate.
Hey…
how could I turn a blind eye
when my subordinate got beat up?
By none other than
my nutcase ex-boyfriend?
- "Nutcase"?
- Yes, a nutcase!
I had a terribly shameful
office romance with you.
Why would I do that again? Are you nuts?
- Well, that--
- And…
me kissing someone
is none of your business.
- Hey!
- What?
I'm worried about you.
Men know what men are like.
That punk, Si-woo, is a jerk.
I wasn't going to tell you this,
but do you know what he did at my wedding?
If you were such a good guy,
why did you marry someone else
after mailing out our wedding invitations?
Hey, I couldn't help it because of Yu-jin.
But he's using you to get back at me.
So you're worried about me?
Of course, I am.
No, you're worried about people
talking about you if I date Si-woo.
That's part of the reason too.
Wouldn't you be bothered by it?
- Hey!
- What?
Get lost.
Ha-kyung, you can't date him!
He's not the one for you!
Gosh, she's a half-wit.
He's really trying to get back at me!
Seriously.
You look so happy to have the weekend off.
Of course. I haven't had
the weekend off in so long.
Honestly…
I have no one to hang out with
when I have a weekday off.
I wish I was free on my day off.
When I have a weekend off,
I have to look after my kids all day.
I have to take them out to eat
and on field trips.
Working is more relaxing.
I see.
I think I know
what Senior Forecaster Um is going to do.
What are you doing tomorrow?
I'm going on a date.
I hear there's a good musical.
I love musicals. What's it called?
The title is…
- Emergency.
- "Emergency"?
"Emergency"?
- I've never heard of it.
- Sorry?
It's a small theater musical.
A small theater.
What's wrong?
What about you, Assistant Director Shin?
I don't do anything special on weekends.
I make coffee first thing in the morning.
Ki-jun found out.
How?
- I like smelling coffee in the morning.
- He saw us together in the restaurant.
So what did you tell him?
I told him we weren't dating.
I eat a simple salad for breakfast.
After I work out, I clean the house.
Do you think he'll believe that?
Why don't we just come out?
We have to play innocent.
I eat when the food comes.
After lunch…
Let's not go to Daehangno tomorrow.
Why not?
Ki-jun's favorite
spicy chicken place is there.
He goes there from time to time.
He might be there tomorrow.
Classical pianists have
different brain structures.
Actually…
I had a hard time getting the tickets.
Do you want to run along the Han River?
Even if it's the same piece…
No. For the time being,
outdoor activities are prohibited.
But we can't stay home.
The biggest difference is that
jazz pianists have good reactivity
and classic pianists have accuracy.
It's interesting.
Depending on what genre you specialize in,
the brainwave displays differently.
It can apply to us.
We're all weather forecasters,
but local forecasters…
CONTINUOUS HEATWAVE…
JIN HA-KYUNG?
Do you know who he's dating right now?
Who is he dating?
Jin Ha-kyung.
Nonsense.
- What is?
- What?
- What's nonsense?
- It's nothing.
MOTHER-IN-LAW
Hello, ma'am. How are you?
Pardon?
Oh, I'm sorry. I forgot.
I'll tell Ki-jun.
Yes.
Yes, I'll see you on the weekend.
Okay.
Where are you going?
- I'm going shopping.
- Shopping?
Hi, Tae-kyung.
Mom wants you to come by after work.
I'm busy.
If you don't come,
Mom will go to your place.
- Do whatever--
- Si-woo.
What should we have for dinner?
How about budaejjigae?
Do you know how to make it?
- I'll be right there. Bye.
- Well, I know how to order it.
- That's weird.
- What is it?
She can't come?
- She'll be here.
- What?
Mom.
Will you really have it out with her?
Just give up.
How can I? She's my daughter.
What else should we get?
- Dumplings.
- Dumplings?
- Do we have instant noodles at home?
- Yes.
We're ordering budaejjigae.
What toppings do you want?
I need to go to my mother's.
Enjoy your dinner.
To her mother's?
- Did something happen?
- I don't know.
Where should I go
for the field trip assignment this time?
Where are you?
I'm at work of course.
I told you he left earlier.
Where in the world is he staying?
Mom?
Yes?
Nothing. I'll take care of it.
- What is it?
- A field trip.
I know where to go.
Think of it as your mother's last wish.
Just three blind dates.
Yes, Ha-kyung. Try it.
I told you no.
Will you let my money go to waste?
What about my time that'll go to waste?
So…
just go on only three blind dates.
Who knows? You might find the right one.
They say that people who get married
through matchmaking services
have a lower divorce rate
than those who get married after dating.
Why are you looking at me?
Hot romance?
It's meaningless.
Look at her. She acted like
she couldn't live without him,
but she got divorced within a year.
Why do you have to bring that up?
Jeez!
Don't hold memorial services
for me after I'm dead.
Be good to me while I'm alive, okay?
Okay?
How dare you!
It's your mother's last wish
before she dies.
How can you say no just like that?
How?
My goodness. How can you say no so easily?
Stop forcing me to get married.
My goodness.
- I'm leaving.
- Don't be like that.
She's acting like that
because she's really worried.
We are her only children.
Her elder daughter got divorced,
and her younger daughter
broke off her engagement.
I guess she wants us to have someone
to lean on before she dies.
Just grant her wish.
You guys can get married then.
Hey, don't say that.
Do you know how I feel when Mom does this?
I feel like I'm being driven
to the edge of a cliff.
If she really cares about me,
she shouldn't make me feel like this.
Yes. You're right.
Anyway, I hate feeling like this. Bye.
Mom.
Were you happy
when you were married to Dad?
What kind of stupid question is that?
No marriage is always happy.
There are good times and bad times.
When all is said and done,
two is better than one,
and three is better than two.
My friend Mi-jeong's youngest daughter
said she'd live alone forever.
But look at her.
She's happily married with children.
Her husband has a stable job too.
Your friends' daughters
and Ha-kyung may be different.
Maybe she's better off alone.
What?
It just crossed my mind.
Good night.
You must be tired from being angry.
Hi.
Your mom called this afternoon.
She wants to have dinner with us tomorrow.
You can come, right?
Did you go shopping again?
- That's not--
- You're so carefree.
Aren't we on a tight budget
because the rent is so high?
We can take out another loan
to pay for the key money,
but you know we need money
for the moving expenses.
Are you saying that
I'm spending thoughtlessly?
If you aren't
you wouldn't have bought
something that expensive.
- Ki-jun.
- Let's not do this.
I don't want to fight.
I'm washing up.
Did something happen at home?
Kind of.
You don't have to worry though.
If you're tired,
we can just hang out at home tomorrow.
Can you come out to the living room?
Do you want some beer?
No, thank you.
I'm good.
I guess we can't stay home.
Right?
Let's avoid crowded places.
Is there any place that's especially quiet
when it rains?
There is one place.
- Where?
- Do you like nature?
Of course.
Can you stand being uncomfortable?
To a certain extent?
Good then.
Where is he going to take me?
What's wrong with you?
It's your day off, right?
We need to talk.
Come to the brunch café when you wake up.
I'll be waiting for you.
No.
You're here.
Lee Si-woo.
- Hi.
- Shall we go?
What?
"Colleagues"?
I'll catch you red-handed.
Where are they going?
Damn it.
HONEY
Where are you? Did you forget
that we're visiting your mom?
We have to leave before 6 p.m.,
so come home before then.
There's enough time.
The traffic is getting better now.
- Where are we going?
- We're almost there.
I hope you like it.
- Thanks.
- You can go that way.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Who pooped here…
Jeez.
HONEY
It's really nice.
- Aren't you glad we came?
- Yes.
- Isn't it too heavy?
- No, it's okay.
Why won't he text me back? Where is he?
The person you are trying to reach
is unavailable. Please leave a message…
We have to go to Camping Site B.
We should go that way.
It's a little far.
It's okay. We can walk.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Do you need help?
- No.
- Will you be okay?
- Yes.
Let's go.
It looks light. Let me get on.
Are you going to sit there? I'll pull you.
I'll collect evidence
so she can't deny it.
Where's my phone?
There's enough time.
Damn it! Why did I leave it there?
Did she go somewhere?
Si-woo, did you eat?
Should we go out
and grab something to eat?
Jeez. I guess they're both out.
Well…
MOBILE DISASTER PREVENTION
AND WEATHER SYSTEM
NO CONNECTION
That's weird. There's no connection.
The internet isn't working, right?
No.
He said it'd work.
I just want to check
the real-time conditions.
Hold on a second.
- What is it?
- Seok-ho.
Can you check the radar, please?
You can do it yourself.
I'm outside and there's no internet here.
Please do me a favor.
Wait.
What did he say?
He'll check. Give me your phone.
Right now
the stationary front is moving north.
Jeju is getting 5mm of rain
and the South Sea is getting a few drops.
Okay.
Raindrops are falling in Jeju
and the southern regions.
Seok-ho, hold on.
Ask him for the NWP model from 1 p.m. too.
The NWP model too?
Who are you with?
My girlfriend.
Then forget about it
and focus on your date.
Chief Team One will monitor
the real-time situation.
- Bye.
- Okay.
What did he say?
He told me not to worry about it
and do my thing
because there are people
working at the KMA other than me.
I know that. I'm just curious.
Seok-ho is right.
We need to rest
to cheer up and work again.
The stationary front is heading north
as we expected.
So let's forget about it
and focus on each other.
Okay.
- Should I wash these?
- Yes.
Yes.
Chief Team One will do a good job.
A vanilla latte with soy instead of milk
and add only two syrups please.
I'll use my coupon.
- What's your name?
- It's Shin Seok-ho.
It's not there.
Not there? I got a stamp the other day.
- From me?
- No, from the other clerk.
Okay.
I'm getting coffee.
I'll check it with my boss later.
Can you pay for this for now?
Excuse me. My coupon is gone.
You said you'd keep it safe.
This isn't right.
What? Apartment number 1302?
Other customers are waiting.
Please check again.
Hello.
Hey. What brings you here?
I'm here to get coffee, of course.
Okay.
What's going on, apartment number 1302?
They lost my fully stamped coupon.
Did you leave it with them?
Well, I already told him
that I couldn't find it
at the moment.
I'll check with the manager later,
so if you could pay for it--
I was going to use my coupon,
so I didn't bring my wallet.
- Do you want me to cancel your order?
- Seriously?
- I'll pay for it.
- It's okay.
You helped me last time.
What did you order?
A vanilla latte with soy instead of milk
and two pumps of syrup.
That and one cool, iced Americano please.
I'll pay for them both.
Okay.
Well…
"cool, iced Americano"
is an incorrect expression
because iced means it's already cool.
- Don't you think I know that?
- Right.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
One chamomile, please.
Wait! Sir!
Wait!
My car!
Wait! Wait for me!
Hey!
What?
I can't stop thinking about it.
It'll rain, right?
It will. The sky is so dark.
It'll rain.
Hey.
You're curious too.
Let's do this. Give me your phone.
Whoever picks up their phone first
has to do the dishes.
Okay, then…
don't we need to cook first?
Camping is all about barbecue.
Okay.
What did you bring?
What?
What is it?
I thought I packed meat.
It's okay.
Camping is all about having kimchi stew.
We have nothing to make broth with.
Should I go and get some meat?
It's okay. All we need is kimchi.
It's okay.
How is it coming along?
- Is it good?
- I don't know.
I haven't tasted it yet.
- You're a good cook.
- Try it.
- Can I?
- Yes.
- It's good.
- Is it?
Try it.
- Isn't it good?
- I think I'm a genius.
It's good.
Stay there. Look here.
VEHICLES SUBJECT TO FINES AND TOWS
HONEY
- Hey.
- Where are you?
- Well, Yu-jin…
- I'll go straight to your mother's.
Meet me there, okay?
Don't be late.
Where have you been?
What happened to you?
Something happened.
Did you forget what today is?
It's your mother's birthday.
Hey.
Why do you have to say "your mother"?
You can just call her Mother or Mom.
She called me two days ago
to have dinner with us.
Where have you been all day?
Do you know how awkward it was?
Did Mom say something?
Where have you been?
Do I need your permission
whenever I go somewhere?
There was something
very important that I needed to check.
Don't tell me
you went to see Ha-kyung again.
You said you couldn't believe
that they were together.
Is that so important to you?
You even forgot your mom's birthday.
Why?
When I broke off the engagement
with Ha-kyung and married you,
people said nasty things about me.
They said it was
as if I dumped a faithful wife.
They also called me a two-timer
who made a shameless transfer.
I had to hear all kinds of terrible names.
I can't let Ha-kyung
act like she's a victim.
She's dating none other
than Si-woo, that jerk!
Ki-jun.
I want you to focus on our problem.
There are so many issues to solve.
Exactly.
I need to take care of this
so I can focus on other things, Yu-jin.
So what will you do?
Will you tell everyone?
Why not?
If you do,
people will talk about us too.
Haven't you thought about that?
Be honest.
Stopping her from acting like
a victim is an excuse.
Aren't you just jealous
because they're going out?
Jealous?
Of Si-woo?
Why would I be?
You must know why better than I do.
It's not raining.
It's not.
It doesn't look like it will.
It probably won't.
What time is it?
It's 20:21.
We're doomed.
Cheers.
INNOVATIVE WEATHER SERVICES
A STEPPING STONE TO PUBLIC SAFETY
The meeting started ten minutes ago.
Okay.
The NWP model showed that
the stationary front was moving north.
Why isn't it raining?
Due to the abnormal development
of anticyclone over the Okhotsk Sea
and the cold air in the north,
the northward movement
of the stationary front is being delayed.
Isn't that what Senior Forecaster Um was
worried about in the last meeting?
It is.
When will it rain?
We're expecting it
to come early next week.
But if this continues,
the possibility of further delay
can't be ruled out.
Goodness.
First of all,
send explanatory data to the media
about why the rain is delayed.
Let's do our best
to monitor the situation.
- Okay.
Wouldn't it be better to mention
the possibility of dry changma
for the sake of the future?
- "Dry changma"?
- Yes.
We can't do that because
the stationary front is still there.
Even if it is cloudy and there is no rain,
there's a higher chance of precipitation.
So it's wrong
to make a hasty announcement.
Isn't making hasty conclusions
your specialty?
What is it?
Is your hunch not working this time?
Even that hunch
is based on data and meteorological flow.
Either it's right or wrong.
I can't give out vague information
just because
I'm afraid of being criticized.
"Vague information"?
Doesn't "for the sake of the future"
mean "vague information"?
What are they doing?
That's enough.
No. Keep going.
Pardon?
I said keep going.
Why don't you two have a debate about it?
Come up with a conclusion too.
We'll release that conclusion
with explanations to the press.
That'd be good, right?
What?
Is there a problem?
No, there isn't. We'll do that.
Okay. Keep going.
Director Jin.
I'll be back.
Will you be okay?
Yes.
First, let's analyze
why this forecast was wrong.
Aren't we coming up with an explanation
for why the rainy season is delayed?
We need to review starting
from the initial forecast
and see what we missed.
Only then can we explain the gap
between the expected and actual dates.
Okay.
Where should we start?
During the early forecast,
why did you predict
that rain from the stationary front
would fall in Jeju and the southern part
of Korea five days later?
If you look at the strong wind
at 200hPa above the stationary front
and the speed of the anticyclone
of the North Pacific,
there was a possibility of development.
The explanation isn't out yet?
No.
Do you know
why it's being delayed?
I guess they're revising it.
I'm right.
Look at this.
This upper part is strong,
so the lower can't move up.
I'm right.
- It's too weak.
- Mr. Lee, look.
This front isn't able to move up
because of the anticyclone.
That's why it's not happening.
You're missing that.
- Hello.
- Where is Forecaster Lee?
- Well…
he's at the Office of Spokesperson
preparing the explanation.
He said he sent the details
of today's work to your email.
- Here it is.
- Okay.
- Good work.
Good work.
Don't worry.
- Doors closing.
- They won't fight again.
Let's grab dinner.
- Okay.
- I want something refreshing.
- Like what?
Cold noodles.
It was wrong to analyze that
the stationary front was moving north
due to the trough and strong winds
in the central-northern region of China.
Anyone would have made that conclusion.
Senior Forecaster Um's theory
that the stationary front
would move south made sense,
but the probability was low.
You said you trusted your hunch.
But when you had to take responsibility,
you went with probability.
Isn't that a lame excuse?
Because I wasn't sure.
Someone told me that it was too risky
to go with my intuition
because the safety of too many people
was at stake.
Then why are you taking
a risk with Ha-kyung?
She looks strong,
but she's actually tender-hearted.
She must have had
a hard time because I hurt her.
We're working on explanatory data.
If you're dating Ha-kyung
because you're mad at me or my wife…
you should stop seeing her.
Ha-kyung never does anything poorly.
If she really did start something,
then she must be sincere.
So if she gets hurt again,
she might not be able to recuperate.
You're the one who hurt her.
Don't you think you're being too nosy?
Exactly.
Because I hurt her,
I'm worried about her too.
Don't worry.
I'm also the type of person
who doesn't start something
if I'm not sincere about it.
Release this as an explanation.
I'll get going then.
By the way…
See you next week, Seong-jun.
Bye.
Why…
did you break up with him?
What?
Honestly, he seems like a good man.
No…
he is a good man.
Why did you leave him and come to me?
Don't you know?
No.
I really don't.
You asked me to marry you.
You were the first.
You were the first man to ask me
to marry him, not just date.
I'm sorry.
You married
a penniless bloke.
That's why you're not
registering our marriage.
Why are you so pathetic?
Do you think that's why I put off
our marriage registration?
Then why?
Honestly…
you haven't really focused on us
since we got married.
You're worried about
what others think of our marriage.
Now you're so concerned
about Ha-kyung dating Si-woo
that you can't even focus on anything.
How can I register our marriage
when I'm not sure
if you even love me anymore?
How can I trust you?
Don't make excuses.
There's only one reason.
Keep your eyes on me.
You said you loved me.
Did something happen with Ki-jun?
I want to do better.
- What?
Let's analyze
- the stationary front again.
- Why?
Did you catch a strange signal?
No, I found something when I was
working with Deputy Director Han.
Here.
The Okhotsk air mass,
which has been developing abnormally,
is stopping its expansion.
There's also an inflow
of water vapor from the southwest.
Isn't it still too weak
to activate the anticyclone
of the North Pacific?
- What do you think?
- I agree with you.
Take a look at this part.
Don't you think
the rain particles are getting larger?
It's uncertain.
If the anticyclone over
the Okhotsk Sea stops developing
and water vapor continues
to flow in from the southwest,
the anticyclone of
the North Pacific will expand.
Then I think
it'll definitely rain in two days.
Let's go with
Forecaster Lee's forecast this time.
Because water vapor is flowing in
from the south.
If you say so. Okay.
Thank you for trusting me.
INNOVATIVE WEATHER SERVICES
A STEPPING STONE TO PUBLIC SAFETY
THE KMA'S WEATHER FORECAST
IS WRONG AGAIN
THE FORECAST IS WRONG AGAIN
WHAT IS THE PROBLEM?
The KMA's forecast was wrong again.
What's the reason?
As global warming accelerates,
the variables of the prediction,
including natural cycle fluctuations
such as El Niño and La Niña,
have become much more complex.
Can you put it simply?
It's like having to guess
the path of a vehicle
that ignores traffic signals
and driving lines.
The reporters are excited.
Because there haven't been
any events or incidents lately.
Director Jin has been
having a hard time since she got promoted.
Nothing's going her way.
Aren't you tired?
Let's go inside.
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't insisted,
we wouldn't have been wrong.
You weren't wrong.
Senior Forecaster Um
and I weren't right either.
Like you said,
weather is about variability.
A small thing
can change everything.
What should we do now?
We got it wrong, so we have to be scolded.
THE KMA'S ERRONEOUS FORECAST
The KMA predicted that
it would rain 50 to 100mm per hour
in Seoul, Gyeonggi,
and Yeongseo in Gangwon Province,
starting this morning.
However, until now,
most of the regions are only cloudy.
Thankfully, there wasn't a storm
on the way to work,
but people are tired of the KMA's
- erroneous forecasts.
- Bo-mi.
I have a headache.
Okay.
- The KMA's forecast was wrong again.
- Wait.
What's the reason?
As global warming accelerates,
the variables of the prediction,
including natural cycle fluctuations
such as El Niño and La Niña,
have become much more complex.
It's like
having to guess the path of a vehicle
that ignores traffic signals
and driving lines.
- It sounds difficult.
- Do you know her?
- Yes.
- Aren't supercomputers
with a huge amount of data
able to predict even such variables?
Thank you. See you next time.
You said that the difficulty
of weather forecasting has increased
due to the rapidly changing climate.
Shouldn't you come up with a solution?
So we try to use a lot of NWP model data
to forecast with more
diverse possibilities in mind.
So there's no clear solution?
We'll try harder.
Trying harder is easy.
Doing it well is difficult.
Are we done?
- Yes.
- Goodbye then.
I heard you were dating Si-woo.
Did Ki-jun say that?
I'm sure I told him we weren't.
He's charming.
He's innocent, yet smart.
He has nothing to show for,
but he has high self-esteem.
He's really good looking too.
May I ask you something?
Why did you break up with him?
Was it because of his father?
Do you think you're all that?
Si-woo's father
isn't a good man.
But he wasn't the reason
I broke up with Si-woo.
Then why…
Si-woo…
doesn't believe in marriage.
He doesn't want to marry anyone.
By the way,
Ha-kyung doesn't sincerely date anyone
if they're not a marriage prospect.
You knew that, right?
Doors opening.
Going up.
Hold on.
Sure.
Hello.
Like how flowers bloom in spring
and how the rainy season brings
a downpour of rain in summer,
for me,
marriage was a natural thing
to do when the time came.
As the climate is changing
and the uncertainty
of weather forecasting is increasing…
Si-woo…
doesn't believe in marriage.
He doesn't want to marry anyone.
…nothing can be taken for granted.
I've never thought about a relationship
that didn't lead to marriage.
Who are you? My daughter lives here.
- What?
- Hey.
You two are living with my daughter?
Was that man we met in the elevator
your colleague as well?
- Thank you.
- Wait.
Are you the eldest son?
Why do you ask?
What's with Yeouido's current temperature?
Remove the information
from the prevention portal site.
The incorrect information
on the portal site.
You told him, didn't you?
You should have reported it
to me right away!
Subtitle translation by: Soo-hyun Yang